BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13) 6178/013
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13)
1950- 1974
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States Department of Labor
Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS)
6178/013
3.5 cubic feet
3.5 linear ft.
Records (documents), collective labor agreements.
5833681
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 30, 2005
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 21, 2016
Biographical / Historical
The US Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) was established in 1884 to collect information about employment and labor in the United States. As mandated by the 1947 Taft-Hartley Act, the BLS was formally tasked with responsibility for soliciting, collecting, and analyzing collective bargaining agreements (CBAs) from public and private establishments, and making the agreements publicly available. In the early 1980s, this was function was limited to union contracts made with employers of 1000 or more employees.
In 2002, the National Archives and Records Administration authorized the BLS to donate inactive, non-confidential agreements which were 5 years or more past their expiration date to the Kheel Center where they would be preserved and made available to the public. The Office of Labor-Management Services took over responsibility for collecting and analyzing CBAs in 2011, and continues this donor relationship with the Kheel Center.
Scope and Contents
The US Department of Labor Historical Collective Bargaining Agreements Collection, 6178, is made up of 21 series of expired public- and private-sector collective bargaining agreements dating from 1887 to 2003 and totals 685 linear feet plus 10 CDs of digitized documents and 320 reels of microfilm. In addition to the CBAs, a small volume of related documents such as union constitutions, pension and health plans submitted to the BLS, are also available.
Selected collective bargaining agreements from this collection were digitized with generous funding from the National Historic Publications and Records Commission (NHPRC), and the National Science Foundation (NSF). Because documents other than collective bargaining agreements were also collected and preserved here by the US Department of Labor, a folder containing material that has been digitized, may also contain material which has not been digitized such as constitutions, bylaws, working rules, life insurance plans, or other organizational documents. For access to non-digitized material, contact Kheel Center staff.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6178/001: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1) 6178/002: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/003: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/004: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/006: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 6) 6178/007: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 7) 6178/008: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/009: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/010: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/011: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 11) 6178/012: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/014: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14) 6178/015: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15) 6178/016: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16) 6178/017: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/018: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/019: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/020: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/021(d): BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 21) Digital 6178/022 mf: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm 6178/023: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 23)
Arrangement
Series I: Industry Code #21, Mining, Quarrying, and Oil and Gas Extraction
Series II: Industry Code # 22, Utilities
Series III: Industry Code # 23, Construction
Series IV: Industry Code #31, Manufacturing
Series V: Industry Code #32, Manufacturing
Series VI: Industry Code #33, Manufacturing
Series VII: Industry Code #42, Wholesale Trade
Series VIII: Industry Code #44, Retail
Series IX: Industry Code #48, Transportation and Warehousing
Series X: Industry Code #49, Transportation and Warehousing
Series XI: Industry Code #51, Information
Series XII: Industry Code #54, Realt Estate and Rental and Leasing
Series XIII: Industry Code #56, Administrative and Support and Waste Management and Remediation Services
Industrial relations-- United States; Collective labor agreements --United States; Labor unions -- United States; United States. Department of Labor -- Archives; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics -- Archives; International Brotherhood of Teamsters -- Archives; Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America -- Archives; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers -- Archives; Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union -- Archives; International Association of Machinists -- Archives
5833681
- Series I: Industry Code #21, Mining, Quarrying, and Oil and Gas Extraction
  - Code no.560661: Mobil Oil Corporation and Associated Petroleum Employees Union, 1965-1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Code no.570308: Pan American Petroleum Corporation, Fort Worth Division and Independent Oil Workers Union, Local 14, 1965- 1971 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Series II: Industry Code # 22, Utilities
  - Code no.560975: Northwest Natural Gas Company and International Chemical Workers Union, Local 133, 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Code no.651420: Commonwealth Edison: Removed (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Code no.561613: Northern States Power: Removed (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Series III: Industry Code # 23, Construction
  - Code no.531648 / 8858: General Contractors of America, Alaska Chapter and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 959, 1963- 1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Code no.550587: Greater Miami, Broward, Monroe, Chapters, Painting and Decorating Contractors and Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers of America, Council 56, 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Code no.550869: Management Services, Inc. of Tennessee and Knoxville Building Trades Council, 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Code no.551332: Associated Plumbing Contractors of Pittsburgh, Inc. and Journeymen Plumbers' Local Union 27, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Code no.551496: Associated General Contractors of Amercia: Removed, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Scope and Contents
    Now Code no.8864
  - Code no.551545: Electrical Contractors of Louisville, Kentucky and Vicinity and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 369, 1965- 1967 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Code no.551930: Allied Construction Industries of Delaware, Inc. and International Union of Operating Engineers, Locals 542A, 542B, 1965- 1971 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Code no.552279: Master Builders' Association of Western Pennsylvania, Inc. and Cement Masons' Local 526, 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Code no.552280: Master Builders' Association of Western Pennsylvania, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Joint Council of Teamsters, No. 40 of Pittsburgh and Vicinity, 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Code no.552338: Associated General Contractors of America, Inc., Alabama Branch and Structural Ironworkers Local 92, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Code no.552339: Associated General Contractors of America, Inc., Alabama Branch and International Union of Operating Engineers, Locals 312,320,653, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Code no.560015: Industrial Contractors and Builders Association of Indiana and Technical Engineering Division, Local Union 130, 1965- 1972 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Code no.560402: Master Builders' Association of Western Pennsylvania, Inc. and Pile Drivers' Local 2264, 1964-1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Code no.560907: Building Trades Employers' Association of Western Massachusetts, Inc. and Massachusetts Laborers' District Council, Local 999, 1965-1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Code no.561383: General Contractors' Association of New Haven, Inc. and Construction and General Laborers' Local Union 455, 1965- 1970 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Code no.571076: Coal Mine Construction Contractors Association, Inc. and United Mine Workers of America, International Union of District 50 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Code no.580195: Minneapolis Association of Plumbing Contractors, Inc. and United Assoc. Plumbers Local 15, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Code no.590037: Building Trades Employers' Association of Western Massachusetts, Inc. and Massachusetts Laborers' District Council, Local 596, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Code no.590056: Air Conditioning and Refrigeration Contractors of Utah and Locals 19, 47, 348, 466, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Series IV: Industry Code #31, Manufacturing
  - Code no.541862: Utah-Idaho Sugar Company and American Federation of Grain Millers, Locals 288,289, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Code no.551091: Sausage Manufacturers, San Francisco and Sausage Makers' Union, Local 203, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Code no.551340: Ward Foods, Inc. and American Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union, Local 68, 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Code no.551553: Seabrook Farms Co., Inc. and Amalgamated Food and Allied Workers Union, Local 56, 1965-1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Code no.551945: Celanese Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America, Local 1191, 1965-1971 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Code no.560716: G.A. Neuburger Company and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Local 282, 1958-1961 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Code no.560923: Denison Hide Company and Association Employees Organization, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Code no.561015: Heinz USA, of H.J. Heinz Company and Meat and Cannery Workers Union, Local 34, 1968-1974 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Code no.561287: Oberman Manufacturing Company and Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1965-1969 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Code no.561673: Julian and Kokenge Company and Boot and Shoe Workers' Union, Local 241, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Code no.561679: Maybury Shoe Company of Rochester, New Hampshire and Square Deal Organization, Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Code no.570203: Liggett and Myers Tobacco Co. and International Association of Machinists, Local 757, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Code no.570347: Gorton's of Gloucester, Inc. and Seafood District Local 15, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Code no.570874: Marhoefer Packing Company and United Packinghouse Food and Allied Workers, Local 105, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Code no.571201: American Millinery Manufacturers Association, Inc. and United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union, Local 92, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Code no.580086: Chicago Rawhide Manufacturing Company - Elgin Division and Elgin Rawhide Employees Association, Local 221, 1967- 1970 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Code no.580184: Agway Incorporated, Feed Division and American Federation of Grain Millers, Local 306, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Code no.590132: Kitchens of Sara Lee, Inc. and Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union of America, Local 2, 1968- 1971 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Code no.590150: Stokely-Van Camp, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters ,Local 487, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Code no.590186: Samuels Shoe Company and Joint Council No. 25 Boot and Shoe Workers' Union, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Series V: Industry Code #32, Manufacturing
  - Code no.541338: American Standard: Removed, 1950-1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Plant closed
  - Code no.541462: Quaker City Lumber Products Association and Metropolitan District Council of the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Code no.541818: E.I. Du Pont de Nemours and Co. and Chemical Workers Association, Inc., 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Code no.550021: Cyanamid Company and International Union of District 50, United Mine Workers of America, Local 12893, 1964- 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Production and Maintenance
  - Code no.550022: Cyanamid Company and International Union of District 50, United Mine Workers of America, Local 12893, 1964- 1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Laboratory and Clerical
  - Code no.550431: General Industries Co. and Mechanics Education Society of America, 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Code no.550795: Cyanamid Company and Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-241, 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Code no.551311: Kelly-Springfield Tire Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 746, 1964- 1970 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Code no.551565: Pittsburgh Plate Glass Company and Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers of America, Local 8-2340, 1965-1971 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Code no.551581: St. Regis Paper Co. and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 56, 1965-1971 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Code no.551969: Kuthe Laboratories, Inc. and International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, Local 415, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Code no.560168: Sheller Manufacturing Corporation - Dryden-Chicago Division and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 108, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Code no.560642: Stylon Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America, Local 1251, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Code no.560867: Packaging Corporation of America and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 198, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Code no.560899: Bridgeport Tile Contractors Association and Bricklayers, Masons, Plasterers, Cement Finishers, Marble Masons, Tile Layers, Terrazzo Workers International Union, Local 2, 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Code no.561092: Shell Chemical Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers, International Union, Locals 1-5, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Code no.561282: Pure Oil Company, Toledo Refinery and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers, International Union, Local 7-346, 1964- 1966 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Code no.561421: Paper Manufacturers of Holyoke, MA and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Code no.561670: Linoleum, Carpets, Rugs, and Tile Shops and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, District Council of the Providence, Pawtucket and Central Falls Carpenters, 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Code no.561717: Continental Oil Company and Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 2-470, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Code no.561781: Nashua Corporation and International Brotherhood of Bookbinders, Local 33, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Code no.570019: General Refractories Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 2115, 1966-1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Code no.570051: Chess and Wymond Company and Coopers' International Union of America, Local 39, 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Code no.570062: Seattle Rubber Plate Company and Printing Specialties Union, Local 380, 1971-1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Code no.570308: Pan American Petroleum Corporation, Fort Worth Division and Independent Oil Workers Union, Local 16, 1967- 1969 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Code no.570388: Shell Oil Company, Wood River, Illinois Refinery and AFL-CIO, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Code no.570471: Bemis Bro. Bag Company and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Local 341, 1965- 1967 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Code no.570534: Pittsburgh Plate Glass Company, Chemical Division and International Chemical Workers Union, Local 45, 1966- 1970 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Code no.570581: Phillips Petroleum Company, Manufacturing Department and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 351, 1967- 1968 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Code no.570584: Phillips Petroleum Company, Philblack Plant and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 351, 1967- 1969 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Code no.570586: Phillips Petroleum Company, Plains Plant and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 351, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Code no.570587: Phillips Petroleum Company, Plains Butadiene Plant and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 351, 1967- 1969 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Code no.570648: Case Brothers, Inc. and Case Employees Association, Inc., 1966-1970 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Code no.570853: Weyerhaeuser Company and International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, Local 126, 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Code no.570911: West Coast Envelope Employers Council and Printing Specialties Union, Locals 362 and 382, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Code no.570912: West Coast Envelope Employers Council and Printing Specialties Union, Locals 388 and 612, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Code no.571272: Budd Company and United Textile Workers of America, Local 266, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Code no.571277: Gaylord Container Division and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Code no.580033: Northwester Paper Box Company and International Brotherhood of Bookbinders, Local 87, 1968-1971 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Code no.590177: Atlantic Richfield Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL, Local 390, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Code no.590275: Premier Thermo-Plastics Company and International Chemical Workers Union, Local 604, 1968-1971 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Series VI: Industry Code #33, Manufacturing
  - Code no.530260: American Motors Corporation, Milwaukee Body Plant and International Union United Plant Guard Workers of America, Local 555, 1961-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Code no.550490: Christy Corporation and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, Local 449, 1965-1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Code no.550646: Morrison Steel Products Corp. and United Steelworkers of America, Local 3035, 1964-1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Code no.550658: McCord Corporation and International Association of Machinists, Local 2041, 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Code no.550983: Gardner-Denver Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Union, Local 822, 1965- 1971 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Code no.551007: Continental Aviation and Engineering Corporation and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 280, 1965-1971 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Code no.551130: Paris Manufacturing Company and Paris Manufacturing Co. Employees Association, 1962-1970 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Code no.551162: United States Playing Card Company and Playthings, Jewelry, and Novelty Workers Division, Local 256, 1966- 1971 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Code no.551233: Conmar Products Corporation and Margon Corporation and International Association of Machinists, District 47, 1965- 1967 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Code no.551367: Reeves Instrument Division and International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers-CLC, Local 378, 1964- 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Code no.551520: Budd Company and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 757, 1964-1971 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Code no.551617: Reeves Instrument Division and International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, Local 478, 1964- 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Code no.551668: Brockway Motor Trucks, Division of Mack Trucks, Inc. and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 68, 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Code no.552134: Orr and Sembower, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, 1958-1961 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Code no.552321: Sperry Rand Corporation - Remington Office Machines Division and International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, Local 852, 1958-1968 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    1958-1961, 1965-1968
  - Code no.560095: Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Company and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Locals 248,401,487,1027,1036,1316,1319, 1964-1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Code no.560426: Chelsea Products, Inc. and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 61, 1964-1970 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Code no.560443: Louis Marx Company, Inc. and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 116, 1965- 1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Code no.560729: Dayton Tool and Die Works, Inc. and Maintenance and Service Employees Union Local 3, 1965-1971 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Code no.560970: Crosley Division, Avco Corporation and Local Union 1061, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1958- 1966 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Code no.561017: Sargent and Company and United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 243, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Code no.561362: US Steel Corporation - US Steel Supply Division and United Steelworkers of America, 1965-1971 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Code no.561576: American Pulley Company and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, 143, 1966-1971 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Code no.561761: General Dynamics, Fort Worth Division and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 776 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Code no.561863: Monroe International Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, Local 432, 1965- 1969 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Code no.570048: Western Electric Company, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1942, 1966-1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Code no.570204: General Instrument Corporation of Newark, N.J. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1104, 1966- 1970 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Code no.570240: Manitowoc Shipbuilding, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 751, 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Code no.570354: Oilwell Division, US Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Code no.570383: General Electric Company and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 710, 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Code no.570661: Shuron/Continental, Division of Textron, Inc. and Optical Workers' Union, Local 20890, 1966-1970 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Code no.570679: Jamestown Division Art Metal, Inc. and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 1559, District 65, 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Code no.571038: General Motors Corporation and United Plant Guard Workers of America, 1964-1970 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Code no.571071: Speer Carbon Company - Jeffers Electronic Division and United Mine Workers of America, Local 14654, International Union of District 50, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Code no.571151: Republic Aviation Division and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 25, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Code no.580167: Prestolite Company and Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 55, 1968-1974 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Code no.590249: Milton Bradley Company and Milton Bradley Industrial Union, Local 224, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Series VII: Industry Code #42, Wholesale Trade